<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BabyboOH</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="veille_bouton">Start Watch </string>
    <string name="stop_veille_bouton">Stop Watch</string>
    <string name="titre_fragment1">Home</string>
    <string name="titre_activite2">Log Journal</string>
    <string name="titre_activite3">Gallery</string>
    <string name="merci">Your baby is now perfectly safe</string>
    <string name="consigneRecord">Please select the message to play when your baby wakes up or record a new one.</string>
    <string name="consigneRecord2"> Recording in progress! Press the mike button again to stop.</string>
    <string name="record">Start recording</string>
    <string name="stopRecord">Stop recording</string>
    <string name="recordButton"> Record your voice !</string>
    <string name="supConfirm">Do you really want to delete?</string>
    <string name="confirmer">Confirm</string>
    <string name="annuler">Cancel</string>
    <string name="vol">Volume</string>
    <string name="inconnu">Unknown</string>
    <string name="salleEnregistrement">Recording room</string>

    <string name="empty_view_alert">No monster detected yet! Launch a new watch during your baby sleep!</string>

    <string name="oui">YES</string>
    <string name="non">NO</string>

    <string name="sonSelection">was selected.</string>

    <string name="alerte1">Do you want to listen to your message?</string>
    <string name="alerte2">For your baby safety, the watch can\'t be launched on your smartphone if it\'s not on Airplane mode. Do you want to access the airplane menu selection to activate it?</string>
    <string name="alerte3">You\'re leaving the Watch mode, please do not leave your phone near your baby. Your can now de-activate the Airplane mode. Press Yes to access the Airplane menu selection.</string>
    <string name="alerte4">Watch out, all the app datas will be deleted, including monsters and events history. Do you really want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="alerte5">Please name your message (for example mom)</string>
    <string name="quitte_veille_avion">Do not forget to de-activate the Airplane mode to access your phone calls again"</string> 
    
    <string name="title_activity_ecoute">ListeningActivity</string>
    <string name="statistiques_bouton">Log Journal</string>
    <string name="tableau_bouton">Hunting trophies</string>
    <string name="title_activity_enregistrer">RecordActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stats">StatsActivity</string>
    <string name="decibels">Decibels</string>
    <string name="db">dB</string>
    <string name="lux">Lux</string>

    <string name="monstre1_nom">Deedee</string>
    <string name="monstre1_alias">Night Fright</string>
    <string name="monstre1_desc">This monster is a real deal. It has terrified so many children over the years that scientists gave its name to a panik attack symptom.
 If your child survive its encounter, You can be sure he won\'t be afraid of anything ever.</string>
    <string name="monstre1_conditions">It always strikes where and when you don\'t expect it, with a deeply asleep victim, in total darkness. Some say that children who encountered it cried so loud that they were heard from many blocks away. </string>


    <string name="monstre2_nom">Booboo</string>
    <string name="monstre2_alias">The playground terror</string>
    <string name="monstre2_desc">It likes to play it tough but its ginger bread head do not works in its favor. Most children think it\'s a wubby!</string>
    <string name="monstre2_conditions">it may appear at every hour of the day but rarely at night. It provokes mild screaming from children, (they even sometimes laugh!)</string>

    <string name="monstre3_nom">Abracadabranch</string>
    <string name="monstre3_alias">The root beast</string>
    <string name="monstre3_desc">Its multiple branches sing frightening songs. If you hear music coming from your baby\'s room, it might not be his mobile!</string>
    <string name="monstre3_conditions">The root beast lives during the night and is attracted by light. </string>

    <string name="monstre4_nom">Thorny</string>
    <string name="monstre4_alias">The dream eater</string>
    <string name="monstre4_desc">It nourrishes from children\'s dreams. Their nightmares are its candies. If you encounter it in your baby\'s room, do not, under any circumstances, touch it!</string>
    <string name="monstre4_conditions">It appears at night when your child is deeply asleep. Once your baby is awaken, it dashes off quickly.</string>

    <string name="monstre5_nom">Yum Yum</string>
    <string name="monstre5_alias">The voracious</string>
    <string name="monstre5_desc">Watch out! Take good care! In spite of its appearance, this monster is not a nice one. Always hungry, it eats everything it can find. </string>
    <string name="monstre5_conditions">It usually appears during the day at meal time. Beware of the digestion nap!</string>

    <string name="monstre6_nom">EyeSpy</string>
    <string name="monstre6_alias">The day watch</string>
    <string name="monstre6_desc">As a very curious creature, it sticks its only eye everywhere. It\'s very hard to get rid of!</string>
    <string name="monstre6_conditions">It appears at every hour of the day or night, as long as light is on. Usually, children are not really scared of it.</string>

    <string name="monstre7_nom">Puny Sean</string>
    <string name="monstre7_alias">the inside fiend</string>
    <string name="monstre7_desc">It is a master in the art of disguise. When was the last time you took a look under your bed?</string>
    <string name="monstre7_conditions">It is there, everytime and everywhere, so much so that children have gotten use to it. Most of the time, the cries linked to it are weak.</string>

    <string name="monstre8_nom">Dozen-Eye</string>
    <string name="monstre8_alias">Chubbo</string>
    <string name="monstre8_desc">It stays lurking in the dark watching children for hours. Deep down, it likes them (in an affectionate way). It sometimes fantasizes it is a giant teddy bear cuddled by a child\'s loving arms.</string>
    <string name="monstre8_conditions">Mostly shy, it lives in the dark and only comes out at night. </string>

    <string name="monstre9_nom">Skeletic</string>
    <string name="monstre9_alias">BonyExpress</string>
    <string name="monstre9_desc">This terrifying monster is gigantic. It nevertheless usually stays unseen thanks to its ability to crawl on walls like lizards.
 Have you ever look up at the ceiling before leaving your baby\'s room ?</string>
    <string name="monstre9_conditions">It appears at every hour of the day, even in bright daylight! The screamings it provokes can be very intense. It usually walks in company of its eyeblob bush. Watch out if you stumble on it, it might attack you with eyeballs!</string>

    <string name="monstre10_nom">Marsmallow Jones</string>
    <string name="monstre10_alias">The weeper</string>
    <string name="monstre10_desc">Undoubtedly the most lovable monster! It is so scared of children that, when it sees one, it bursts into tears. Don\'t be too harsh on it if you cross its path, it is harmless.</string>
    <string name="monstre10_conditions">It usually gets out when everybody sleeps. It is attracted by nightlights for they comfort it. Keep in mind that if it woke your baby, it surely didn\'t do it on purpose!</string>

    <string name="monstre11_nom">Cuddlator</string>
    <string name="monstre11_alias">The dark embrace</string>
    <string name="monstre11_desc">Beware, this monster tries to pass for you! Its favorite hobby : cuddling, hugging, petting. But when the baby realizes it\'s not you, he usually gets very angry.</string>
    <string name="monstre11_conditions">It likes to get out before naptime or during the evening for it fantasizes that it can help the baby to go to sleep. It also likes to take over from the other monsters in hope to comfort the weeping babies.</string>

    <string name="monstre12_nom">Lamp Ray</string>
    <string name="monstre12_alias">The Bulb</string>
    <string name="monstre12_desc">It shines in the night. The children are drawn to its light and this is probably the most fearful threat.</string>
    <string name="monstre12_conditions">It appears in total darkness, day or night. You will probably want to open up the blinds quickly, won\'t you? </string>

    <string name="title_activity_settings">Set up</string>


    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string-array name="pref_sensibilite_titles">
        <item>high</item>
        <item>normal</item>
        <item>low</item>
    </string-array>
     
    <string-array name="pref_sensibilite_values">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>0</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="pref_declenchement_titles">
        <item>now</item>
        <item>after 15 seconds</item>
        <item>after 30 seconds</item>
        <item>after 1 minute</item>
        <item>after 2 minutes</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="pref_declenchement_values">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>15000</item>
        <item>30000</item>
        <item>60000</item>
        <item>120000</item>
    </string-array>
    

    <string-array name="pref_sexe_titles">
        <item>Girl</item>
        <item>Boy</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sexe_values">
        <item>girl</item>
        <item>boy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_eteint_ecran_title">Authorize screen to turn off</string>
    <string name="pref_eteint_ecran_summary">The screen will turn off during the Watch. Advisable if you want your baby to sleep in a dark room or if you want to save your battery</string>

    <string name="first_time_tittle">Welcome to BabyboOH ! \n\n Our monster hunting team will watch over your baby during his sleep.</string>

    <string name="continuer">NEXT</string>
    <string name="retour">BACK</string>
    <string name="terminer">END</string>
    <string name="ask_genre1">Before starting, we\'d like to know a little more about your little one. Is it...</string>
    <string name="ask_genre2">Is it…</string>
    <string name="fille">a girl ?</string>
    <string name="garcon">a boy ?</string>
    <string name="ask_nom">And what\'s her name?</string>
    <string name="caractere_fille">What a lovely name for a lovely girl!  </string>
    <string name="caractere_fille1"> According to our experts team analysis, it seems that %1$s are great adventurers. With our help, she should be able to come around any night creature!</string>
    <string name="caractere_fille2"> According to our experts team analysis, it seems that %1$s are very pretty princesses. While waiting for prince charming, she\'ll need a little help from us to strike down the monters inhabiting her room!</string>

    <string name="caractere_garcon">What a lovely name for a lovely boy! </string>
    <string name="caractere_garçon1"> According to our experts team analysis, it seems that %1$s are great adventurers! With our help, he should be able to come around any night creature! </string>
    <string name="caractere_garçon2"> According to our experts team analysis, it seems that %1$s are very bright and sensitive boys.  While waiting for him to create his own monster busting machine, he\'ll need a little help from us to strike down the monters hiding under his bed!</string>

    <string name="ask_record1">You just have to record the message that will be played to %1$s and we\'ll have everything we need to watch over %2$s while he sleeps!</string>
    <string name="ask_record2">Press \"continue\" to record the message rightaway or press \"main menu\" to reach app homepage and record the message later.</string>
    <string name="menu_principal">main menu</string>
    <string name="lui">him</string>
    <string name="elle">her</string>
    <string name="bebe_nom">name</string>

    <string name="choix_sexe_toast">Please enter your baby gender to continue</string>
    <string name="entrerNom">Please enter your baby\'s name to continue</string>

    <string name="salle_enregistrement">Recording room</string>

    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>

    <color name="lavande">#E6E6FA</color>

    <color name="gris_material">#E0E0E0</color>
    <string name="title_activity_id_monstre">IdMonstreActivity</string>

    <string name="nom">Name : </string>
    <string name="alias">Aka : </string>
    <string name="description">Description : </string>
   

    <string name="retour_de_ecoute1_garcon">%1$s woke up once during the last watch. A monster was detected! Please connect to the log journal to learn more!</string>
    <string name="retour_de_ecoute1_fille">%1$s woke up once during the last watch. A monster was detected! Please connect to the log journal to learn more!</string>
    <string name="retour_de_ecoute2_garcon">%1$s woke up several times during the last watch over. At least one monster was detected! Please connect to the log journal to learn more!</string>
    <string name="retour_de_ecoute2_fille">%1$s woke up several times during the last watch. At least one monster was detected! Please connect to the log journal to learn more!</string>

    <string name="inconnu_description">Keep on using BabyboOH with your baby. This monster might appear again during the next nap!</string>
    <string name="lancer_enregistrement">Press the mike button to start recording</string>
    <string name="stop_enregistrement">Recording in progress! Press the mike button again to stop</string>

    <!-- Content descriptions -->
    <string name="content_description_veille_bouton">Start watch</string>
    <string name="content_description_apperçu_monstre">Pic of the Monster who woke your baby</string>
    <string name="content_description_photo_monstre">Released monster pic. Click to visualize its ID</string>
    <string name="content_description_stop_veille_bouton">Stop watch</string>
    <string name="content_description_demarrer_enregistreent">Start recording</string>
    <string name="content_description_arreter_enregistreent">Stop recording</string>
    <string name="content_description_gallerie">Gallery</string>
    <string name="content_description_carnet_de_bord">Log Journal</string>
    <string name="content_description_accueil">Home</string>

    <!-- strings de la settings activity
-->
    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">Baby</string>

    <string name="pref_sensibilite_micro">Mike sensitivity</string>
    <string name="pref_sexe">Gender</string>
    <string name="sexe_pref_subtitle">Select your baby gender</string>
    <string name="nom_pref_subtitle">Enter your baby\'s name</string>
    <string name="micro_pref_subtitle">Adjust the mike sensitivity during the watch to prevent too frequent or too seldom sets off</string>
    <string name="declenchement_pref">Message release time</string>
    <string name="declenchement_pref_subtitle">Enter the awaken lapse of time after which you want the song to be played </string>
    
    
    <!-- strings de la detail activity
-->
    <string name="detail_monstre">Monster :</string>
    <string name="detail_date">Date</string>
    <string name="detail_heure">Time</string>
    <string name="detail_duree">Awaken lapse of time</string>
    <string name="detail_luminosite">Brightness</string>
    <string name="detail_decibels">Waking cry</string>
    <string name="detail_highest_decibels">Loudest cry</string>
    <string name="detail_interrompu">Watch over stopped before end</string>
    <string name="ponctuation"> : </string>
    <string name="detail">Wake up details</string>


    <!-- strings de la luminosité
-->
    <string name="noir">Total darkness</string>
    <string name="obscurite">Shadow</string>
    <string name="lumière_faible">Half light</string>
    <string name="lumière_forte">Full light</string>
    <string name="jour">Daylight</string>

    <string name="lancer_veille">Enter to launch the watch</string>

    <string name="son_en_cours">A reading is already in progress</string>
    
 <!-- Pas encore traduit
-->
    <string name="message_to_the_world_garcon">%1$s a été réveillé par un monstre terrifiant nommé %2$s! Merci BabyBoOH de m\'aider à veiller sur mon bébé!</string>
    <string name="message_to_the_world_fille">%1$s a été réveillée par un monstre terrifiant nommé %2$s! Merci BabyBoOH de m\'aider à veiller sur mon bébé!</string>
    <string name="partager">Partager</string>
    <string name="ask_calibre">Pour terminer, nous devons calibrer votre microphone. Pour cette étape, vous devez être dans un endroit silencieux. Pour pourrez recommencer le calibrage plus tard si nécessaire. </string>
    <string name="demarrer_calibrage">Appuyez sur le bouton pour démarrer le calibrage du microphone</string>
    <string name="calibrage_en_cours">Chut...Calibrage du microphone en cours.</string>
    <string name="calibrage_terminé">Le calibrage est terminé. Vous pouvez désormais utiliser BabyboOH avec votre bébé!</string>
    <string name="salle_de_calibrage">Calibrage du micro</string>

    <string name="apropos">A propos</string>
    <string name="a_propos1">BabyboOH Android version 1.0</string>
    <string name="a_propos2">BabyboOH est une application vous permettant de suivre le sommeil de votre bébé de manière ludique. BabyBoOH ne peut en aucun cas se substituer à la surveillance active de la part d\'une personne adulte. Ne laissez pas votre bébé pleurer. Ne laissez pas votre bébé seul. </string>
    <string name="remerciements">BabyboOH a été développé par Nicolas Boutin. Merci à Blandine pour son soutien et ses précieux conseils, à ma soeur Geraldine pour la relecture et la traduction anglaise et à mon frère Jerome pour la conception des dessins de nombreux monstres. Remerciements spéciaux à Mahel pour les discussions enrichissantes et son soutien en territoire hostile. \n\nLa reproduction partielle ou totale du contenu de cette application est interdite.</string>
    <string name="avertissement">Avertissement</string>
    <string name="compris">J\'ai compris</string>
    <string name="ecoute_active">L\'écoute est désormais active</string>
    <string name="sortir">Appuyez sur l\'étoile pour quitter</string>
    <string name="reinitialiser">Réinitialiser l\'application</string>
    <string name="impossible_delete">Vous ne pouvez pas effacer ce son</string>
    <string name="clickToStop">Appuyez à nouveau pour stopper le son</string>
    <!-- Reformulé
-->
    <string name="first_time1">A chaque fois que votre bébé se réveillera, une musique apaisante sera jouée jusqu\'à ce qu\'il se rendorme. Vous pourrez même enregistrer votre propre message en vous rendant dans la salle d\'enregistrement.</string>
    <string name="first_time2">Pour chaque réveil, nos experts analyseront les cris qui ont été émis par votre bébé ainsi que son environnement pour vous dire quel type de monstre l\'a réveillé. </string>

    </resources>
